Our new champions are the Straw Hat Pirates!
Shelly!
What a turn of events!
The captain of the Straw Hats has chosen Shelly,
a horse that Captain Foxy picked up on a whim
after coming to this island.
Is this pure genius or just plain ASE?
There you go, Stiltskai.
Now you have your horse back once and for all.
How can I thank you?
Seeing you together is thanks enough.
This means so much.
Really, thank you.
Well, guess I can't blame him.
Yeah, that is totally what I would have done.
Good girl.
I know you can take it.
After all, you're a man, right?
You bet I am!
That's our Chopper.
Leave it to me, little pal.
You'll be just fine.
If you're Chopper's last hope, he's screwed.
I wonder what the next game's going to be.
Whatever it is, I'm ready for it.
We're going to have Chopper back in no time.
Round three, the round and round roller race.
Shelly, don't worry, girl.
Our friends will be just fine.
All we can do is cheer them on.
Two fried squids and a sausage on a stick.
You got it.
Hey!
We're still missing six support fellas over here!
Hurry it up!
Hey, where'd you guys put my tools?
This next game sounds like fun, don't you think?
Fun?
That's kind of insensitive.
Put yourself in Chopper's shoes for a second.
Poor little guy.
I didn't think of that.
My apologies.
Well, no big deal.
It's these idiots that could use some sensitivity training.
Hello!
You're both so lovely!
Are you ready for the magic?
What are you eating now, Luffy?
It's all kiwi.
That old horse guy gave it to me.
Actually tastes pretty good.
You can't have it.
I don't want it!
It's time for round three, the Run Roll Around roller skating race.
Say that three times fast.
At any rate, it's a head-to-head race on an outdoor track.
As always, the rules are simple.
At the sound of the first whistle,
each team's point-getter will start skating around the track.
Twenty seconds later, the second whistle will blow
and the team defenders will follow suit.
The defenders can try to hinder the opposing team
or support their point-getter.
Anything goes.
Assuming that the point-getters aren't injured or disqualified,
the race will continue for five minutes.
At the end of that time,
the team whose point-getter is in the league wins.
So as little as an inch can mean victory or defeat.
Naturally, yours truly will be providing the play-by-play
from my special bird's nest view
right next to the starting line.
Now it's time for our two talented teams to take the track.
All right, guys.
No matter how bad they cheat,
we gotta get Chopper back this time.
You ready?
Yeah!
Whoa!
And here come the Straw Hat dangers,
making a grand entrance with a roaring battle cry.
And on this end,
their all-powerful opponents,
the indomitable Foxy Devils!
Roostop is the team's playmaker, Porkchop!
Next is the stunningly speedy Cheetah!
The defensive dynamo, Mashikaku!
The fighting fishman, Jube!
And Girarin!
Oh!
And last but not least,
we have Foxy as the head coach
and Hamburg as the team manager!
That's a mighty line-up if I've ever seen one!
Hey, what are you doing?
Whoa!
What is Chicky Cheetah up to?
Is he intimidating Luffy before the start of the match?
What's with this weirdo?
He's kind of creeping me out.
Fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee!
His feet are indeed a thing of wonder,
but his nose is impressive too!
You ate something pungent, didn't you?
Uh-oh, Luffy, he's onto you!
That's what you get for eating that old man's cheese!
Oh, is that why?
That was a joke!
Jeez!
Lots of manners, will ya?
Shoo! Shoo!
Wow!
Okay!
I don't know what that was about!
But anyway, now that that's done with,
let's get back to the rules!
In addition to the defenders and point-getters,
each team also has a coach and a manager,
but unlike the other players,
they're limited to the sidelines!
The teams must change point-getters every round,
and each player can only be point-getter once!
But wait!
Since the manager and coach can't play,
that means you need at least seven members,
which makes the Straw Hats one man short!
Whatever shall they do?
That's a shame!
But hey, since I'm such a generous guy,
I'll let one of you sorry saps be the point-getter twice!
If your pride will allow it, of course.
Fefefefefefefe!
I've had about enough of that laugh!
We love you, boss!
You're the best!
So kind!
The generosity has moved me to tears!
You're a real man!
You guys!
Can you believe this guy? He's actually taking this crap seriously.
Anything to feed his ego, right?
We gotta hurry up and put this guy out of his misery.
Oh, no! Don't sink, boss! We need you!
But, annoying as he is, we kinda have to take him up on his offer, right?
Hey, as long as it helps us beat him faster, I'm not complaining.
We're fighting for Chopper's sake. This is no time to get hung up on pride.
You're on, Splithead. We've got ourselves a match now. Get ready.
You're too naive, boy. Do you want to know why I made you an offer that puts me at a disadvantage?
Simple.
Cause we're awesome!
Alright! Let's get Chopper's sake!
Yeah!
Boss, no!
And there you have it! Both captains have agreed to amend the rules!
As soon as the Straw Hat Rangers select a point-getter for each round, we can begin!
Alright. Since we've got five rounds, our best bet is to put our strongest scores in rounds one, three, and five.
Question is, who do we want to start out with?
Put me in two rounds, okay? Please? Please?
I'll think about it if you shut up and leave me alone for a sec!
Since he's so full of energy, I'll put Luffy as point-getter in round one, then again in round five.
Yeah!
I probably shouldn't expect much from Nami and Usopp.
Hey, Robin. Looks like it's best to put you in round three. That okay?
Sure. You seem to understand this better than anyone else.
Thank you. But wait, what if the other team has the same idea?
Okay, new plan.
Okay, come on! Hurry up!
Alright, I'm done!
Luffy has rounds one and five, Nami has two, Usopp has three, and Robin has been moved to four.
Hey, hold on a sec. Why do you get to make all these big decisions without asking me?
Huh?
Cause the coach makes all the decisions, not the manager. And I'm the coach.
And why do you get to have the awesome job while I get stuck following your stupid orders?
Obviously, because I'm a genius and your brain is so rotten you're growing mold on your head.
If you think you're a genius, then your ego is as twisted as your eyebrows.
Why?
By the way, there's one more very important rule we need to...
Knock it off! I can't heal him!
If any of the racers go and traverse or leave the course for whatever reason,
they will be immediately disqualified from the game.
Starting before the whistle means disqualification as well.
Okay, looks like everything is finally set in the first round.
Oh, coming on strong from the start, it's Straw Hat Movie versus our very own Porcha!
The anticipation is killing me! So without further ado, let's get this thing started!
Man, talk about exciting!
No kidding, this is my favorite event!
Yeah, mine too!
Go Porcha! Beat that rubber dude's sense lift!
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha! Hey, look!
Ha-ha-ha! You're kidding me! The way...
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Whoa! This is kinda hard!
Uh-uh-uh-uh! Please somebody tell me I'm seeing things!
No! Don't make me look! I'm scared! Make it go away!
Ha-ha-uh-uhhh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha!
Ooh!
Please, somebody tell me I'm seeing things!
No! Don't make me look! I'm scared! Make it go away!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Infected? Straw Hat doesn't know how to skate!
And according to the roster, he's scheduled to play Port Kidder in two rounds.
Is the game over before it's even started?
Hey, you can race as many times as you like, kid!
Come on.
Now what are we gonna do?
Wait a second. If we can't count on Luffy, then that means everyone's gonna expect me to win the third round!
Ah!
Both teams have finally made it to the starting line, but I'm beginning to wonder if this is going to be much of a race.
At any rate, let's see what happens, Howie.
Why'd you ask to be in two rounds if you don't even know how to skate?
It's not my fault. That was before I found out that skating is the hardest thing in the world.
We're doomed. It's all over now.
Don't give up just yet. It's our job to pick up the slack.
Come on, guys. Let's go. Quick Air is to the track.
What? Not you again.
If you pull any more stunts, you're getting a boot to the face.
We don't need stunts this time. We can beat you with both hands tied behind our back.
It's time for the third game, the Run Roll Around.
Will Portia breeze through to an easy victory, or will the rookie skater's straw hat make a miraculous improvement?
On your marks, get set.
And she's off! Portia tears down the track with spectacular speed!
Now let's check in on our challenger, Loafy!
He's flat on his face! He didn't even make it across the starting line!
Certainly is hard-headed, isn't it?
Stupid shoes!
Hold now! Removing your skates will result in instant disqualification!
Right!
If I make it over there, I can grab the rail!
Well, not much of a race!
20 seconds have passed!
It's time to let the defenders loose!
I see Gokko!
Hey! He's about to get pinned! Somebody help him!
Not me!
Well, that's weird.
Gum-Gum Balloon?
That's it! Let's go, Usopp!
What?
Hey!
Listen, Loopy, you have to keep holding your breath!
We're gonna roll you all the way around the track!
Whatever works!
Cien fleurs, Delphinius!
Huh?
Wow! Thanks, Robin!
She's rolling it with her arms!
Awesome!
What incredible speed!
You can hardly tell it skating, but he's definitely catching up to Parcha!
Oh, no!
Flowers should have been!
Uh-oh!
Amazing!
This is certainly the most bizarre comeback I've ever seen!
But wait!
The Foxy Devils have lined up some powerful defense!
I am a wolf!
Oh!
But a fancy flying maneuver sends him sadly over Mashikaku!
It's only a matter of time before he catches up to Parcha!
All right, Robin!
Nice!
Not so fast, huh?
Killer!
Sword!
Festival!
Huh?
Oh!
But a fancy flying maneuver sends him sadly over Mashikaku!
It's only a matter of time before he catches up to Parcha!
All right, Robin!
Nice!
Not so fast, huh?
Killer!
Sword!
Festival!
Huh?
What a turn of events!
Straw Hat Luffy has sword his way out of bounds!
Oh, no!
Was that a sword?
Luffy, are you okay?
These things?
Don't worry.
Here, look.
It's fine.
They're nothing but shoe.
I...
I don't feel so good.
You can come down now.
This is bad.
Since we can't count on Luffy, that means me, Robin, and Usopp all have to win.
At this rate, Chopper might not be the only one we lose.
As expected, the winner of the first round is the lovely Parcha!
As you know, that means one point for the Boxy Devils!
I hate skating!
Oh, shut up and get down here!
Now, let's move right along!
In the second round matchup, the Straw Hat Portgetter is Nami!
The nefarious navigator!
She'll be up against the king of defense, Mashikaku, everyone's favorite human role!
Don't worry about losing.
Just focus on the match.
Round two.
On your marks...
Get set...
And they're off!
Or at least Nami is.
Mashikaku, on the other hand...
Well, to put it nicely, let's say he's taking his time.
It looks like the Heartless Witch might be able to win without any conniving this time!
Am I missing something?
Why is he so slow?
It's too quiet.
What's going on?
Is this some kind of trick?
Forget about him, Nami!
Just keep moving!
Right!
And there's the second whistle!
Let's see what we can do.
Wait!
Why aren't they moving?
If you think you can get past us, then be my guest.
You wanna step up to these babies?
Little late to be making a roadblock.
We're the ones in the lead this time.
If you guys don't move, then I will!
Take it easy, Luffy!
We got this one!
Look how slow he is!
There's no way Nami's gonna lose against that guy!
Is that what you think?
Flower hypnosis!
What happened?
We didn't just fall asleep on the track, did we?
I'm not sure.
Luffy!
Guys!
Wake up!
But... they're in the same place as before, right?
Yeah.
Nami!
You're about to lose the race!
You're gonna get moving now!
Five!
Four!
What?
Why would I...
Three!
Two!
One!
The Foxy Devils win two rounds in a row!
One more and it's all over for the dangers!
That can't be.
He's in the same spot, but that's only because he did a whole lap.
Snooze, you lose!
It looks to be you, huh?
Fefefefefefefe!
Can't believe we beat him with Mashikaku!
Are you kidding?
Unless the Straw Hats can pull it together fast, things could be over for them in a flash!
With a two-point deficit, everything is riding on the next round!
We'll lose up's aerodynamic nose!
Give him the edge he needs!
The beep!
But I'm allergic to...
Don't you dare try to tell us you're allergic to roller skates!
Try to tell us you're allergic to roller skates!
How can I beat a guy with cheetah in his name?
Heck, he might even be a cheetah now that I look at him!
Ow!
That's all wrong.
Try to lower your stance a little.
You gotta use your hips when you move.
Never figured you for a skater!
Wow!
I can't rely on Luffy for this one.
What I need is a strategy!
Spread them out a little.
Huh, like this?
Ow!
Not even close.
Like this?
Ow!
No!
Like this?
Ow!
No! Listen to me, dammit!
On your marks!
I've got nothing!
Well, whatever.
I can go faster than a cheetah if I try hard enough, right?
I'm in the lead!
It worked!
So fast!
Your little friend might as well give up now and save himself the effort.
Cheeky Cheetah doesn't even need our help, you know.
This is hopeless!
What am I supposed to do?
No way!
He already finished a whole lap?
Maybe you guys should just sit back and relax, too.
It's not over till it's over, okay?
That's 20 seconds!
It's time for the defense to go!
Come on, Robin!
What?
Well, good luck!
Here comes!
They're gonna do something!
He's gonna let me!
How do you like this?
No way!
Huh?
There ya go.
Now keep it up, just like I said.
Huh?
Look, he's almost there!
Come on, kid! You can do it!
Come on, kid! Come on, kid!
Daddy! Come on, go!
Is he...?
Yeah! Usopp! You're gonna win this!
Hang on, Chopper! We'll get you back!
Next, One Piece, a seriously heated race,
into the final round!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!